



Zavodskov Lev

Male, 25 years, born on 29 July 1997

+7 (918) 3134727 — https://t.me/Fatalwgx nothingfatalleo@gmail.com — preferred means of communication

Reside in: Krasnodar

Citizenship: Russia, work permit at: Russia Willing to relocate, ready for business trips

Desired position and salary

QA engineer

Specializations:

Tester

Employment: full time

Work schedule: remote working, full day

Desired travel time to work: any

Work experience — 1 year 6 months

November 2021 — till now 1 year 3 months

ITTest

QA Engineer

As an outstaff Software QA consultant:

For client A (November 2021 - March 2022):

- Provide remote QA consulting services to a Summit, NJ based company focused on investments solutions for analisys, research and report.
- · Develop and maintain testing documentation
- Data operations, SQL, PostgreSQL, MS SQL, Dbeaver
- DataBase testing, Backend
- TMS: Gitlab, Jira
- Limited Python automation
- Functional and non-functional testing

For client B (March 2022 - Present): //updated 21.07.2022

- Provide remote QA consulting services to a Top-2 Russian IT company based in Moscow
- Develop and maintain testing documentation, Allure Testops, Jira, Confluence
- Quality assurance of development processes and documentation
- Data operations, SQL, PostgreSQL, phppgAdmin, Dbeaver
- RESTful API testing, Postman, Swagger, gRPC, JSON/XML
- · Web, Backend testing
- · Functional and non-functional testing
- Other services: Gitlab, Gitlab's CI/CD, Docker, Kubernetes, kibana, figma, minio, sap

August 2021 — October 2021 3 months

IP Nikolai Krotov

junior QA manual engineer

During individual training with QA testing mentor I have learned and put to practice the following:

- General software testing terms (Testing levels, type, SDLC, STLC etc.)
- Test design technics(equivalence partition, bordering values, decision table, pairwice etc.)
- Manual functional testing of web-services, applications, mobile apps, API-services;
- black/grey/white box testing;

- software development methodologies
- understanding of client-server architecture
- writing/forming checklists, testcases, bugreports;
- Experience working with Postman, SoapUI
- Experience with bugtracking services such as Jira
- Working with Devtools
- Basic knowledge of SQL
- web-traffic interception with Fiddler
- Experience with mobile farms like Browserstack
- Uderstanding of protocols, methods, HTTP requests/responses
- HTML / CSS
- JSON / XML
- Understanding of Software development methodologies, Agile, Scrum

Education

Level

Secondary school

Key skills

Languages

Russian — Native

English — C1 — Advanced

Skills

ОбучаемостьCSS3PythonHTML5Atlassian JiraSQLBusiness EnglishRussianLinuxISONScrumSOAP

Business English Russian Linux JSON Scrum SOAP XML Q
Testing Git REST Selenium Jenkins Selenoid Web testing

Backend testing Automation testing Pytest

Driving experience

Driver's license category B

Further information

Recommendation

Markov Processes International

5

Kevin Elms (Vice President Enterprise Solutions)

About me

More info such as certificates and code examples can be found on my github profile page: https://github.com/Fatalwqx/amazon-automation-tests

Starting as QA trainee have been steadily gaining knowledge and experience to become solid Software QA

engineer. As a part of outstaff company I've worked for American clients on a position of Middle Software QA

Engineer with fully English speaking teams based in US. Have experience with Database testing, data operations,

functional and non-functional testing, automation testing.

Key Skills:

- Independent and Autonomous, fast learning. 100% remote worker whole career
- Test planning, Test case development and maintenance, Specification analysis, Release management,

Regression testing, Test management

- Python, Selenium webdriver, pytest, Jenkins, requests, pydantic, Selene, Allure report, PageObject
- English (C1) https://www.efset.org/cert/QqPVNG
- REST API, Postman, XML/JSON, Swagger, gRPC
- SQL, PostgreSQL, Dbeaver, PhpPgAdmin
- Git, Gitlab, Github, Bitbucket, SourceTree
- Jira, Confluence, Allure, Figma, Kibana, Upsource, Linux
- Experience with testing in CI/CD environment, kubernetes, docker, Gitlab
- Experience with developing automation testing frameworks and implementing CI/CD

Telegram: https://t.me/Fatalwgx